<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>academic on R Machinery</title>
    <link>https://rubenfcasal.github.io/tags/academic/</link>
    <description>Recent content in academic on R Machinery</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>es</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2017-2023 Ruben Fernandez-Casal</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rubenfcasal.github.io/tags/academic/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting started with the Academic framework for Hugo</title>
      <link>https://rubenfcasal.github.io/post/getting-started/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rubenfcasal.github.io/post/getting-started/</guid>
      <description>This post corresponds to an older versión of the Academic framework for Hugo, visit wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-themes and gohugo for updated information.
The Academic framework enables you to easily create a beautifully simple personal or academic website using the Hugo static site generator.
Key features:
 Easily manage your homepage, blog posts, publications, talks, and projects Configurable widgets available for Biography, Publications, Projects, News/Blog, Talks, and Contact Need a different section?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Customizing the homepage with widgets</title>
      <link>https://rubenfcasal.github.io/post/widgets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rubenfcasal.github.io/post/widgets/</guid>
      <description>This post corresponds to an older versión of Hugo, visit the website for updated information.
Homepage widgets display as sections on the homepage. They can be enabled/disabled and configured as desired. Academic has the following widgets available to use:
 About/biography Selected publications Recent publications Recent news/blog posts Projects Selected talks Recent talks Contact Tag cloud Hero (introduction) Custom widget (demonstrated with the teaching example)  The example site that you copied to create your site uses all the different types of widget (except talks), so you can generally just delete the widgets you don&amp;rsquo;t need and customize the parameters of the widgets you wish to keep.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Managing content</title>
      <link>https://rubenfcasal.github.io/post/managing-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rubenfcasal.github.io/post/managing-content/</guid>
      <description>&lt;div class=&#34;alert alert-note&#34;&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This post corresponds to an older versión of the Academic framework for Hugo, visit &lt;a href=&#34;https://github.com/wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-themes&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;wowchemy/wowchemy-hugo-themes&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://gohugo.io&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;gohugo&lt;/a&gt; for updated information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;/div&gt;


&lt;p&gt;This is a brief guide to managing content with the Academic framework. Content can include publications, projects, talks, news/blog articles, and widget pages. After you have read this guide about creating and managing content, you may also be interested to learn about &lt;a href=&#34;https://rubenfcasal.github.io/post/writing-markdown-latex.md&#34;&gt;writing content with Markdown, LaTeX, and Shortcodes&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>